Dr. Gift is a horror, mystery film directed by Abel Berry.
What do you get when you combine an 80's slasher with a haunting ghost story?
Kat, played by Danielle Harris.
Nadia, played by Tatiana Sokolova.
Jill Korek, played by Julie Anne Prescott.
Tony, played by Billy Blair.
Dolittle is a 1998 American fantasy comedy film directed by Betty Thomas, written by Larry Levin and Nat
Mauldin, and starring Eddie Murphy in the title role, along with Ossie Davis and Oliver Platt.
The film is loosely based on the series of children's stories by Hugh Lofting.
Dolittle received mixed reviews from critics and was a box-office
success, grossing $294 million against a $72 million budget.
The film's success generated a theatrical sequel, Dr.
Dolittle 2 (2001), and three films released direct to video: Dr.
Dolittle 3 (2006), Dr.
Dolittle: Tail to the Chief (2008), and Dr.
Dolittle: Million Dollar Mutts (2009).
The tone is dark and mind_bending.